https://oife.org/privacy-policy/

Welcome to Osteogenesis Imperfecta Federation Europe
Facebook ProfileTwitter ProfileYoutube ProfileLinkedIn ProfileInstagram Profile
Privacy Statement from OIFE HomePrivacy Statement from OIFEOsteogenesis Imperfecta Federation Europe (OIFE) collects personally identifying information about various target groups for our contact lists. We do so in order to reach our goals, which includes networking and exchange of news and information between individuals, professionals, organizations and other stakeholders.OIFE does not trade, share or sell personal information with anyone outside the OIFE without your consent.The OIFE seeks to maintain accurate information regarding individuals in our lists. Individuals may update their personal data by contacting the OIFE at office@oife.org.How we store your personal data?OIFE’s administration is based in several different countries. Because we need to access data from different locations, we store our lists containing personal data in Google Drive. The lists containing personal data are stored in a password protected folder, separated from OIFE’s other files which are also stored in Google Drive. A limited number of people from OIFE’s administration have access to the folder containing personal data.OIFE’s Secretary (based in Germany) serves as our lead data protection supervisory authority.What kind of lists we have containing personal data:OIFE delegates & volunteersWhat kind of data we store:NameE-mailPhone numberSkypeIDPurpose of the data: Administration of the OIFE Who can access the data: OIFE’s administration & Social Network Coordinator Note: Contact lists for delegates & volunteers might be shared with delegates & volunteers within OIFE on a need to know basis.Contact persons of OI-groups & volunteers outside OIFEWhat kind of data we store:NameE-mailPhone numberSkypeIDPurpose of the data: Administration of the OIFE Who can access the data: OIFE’s administration & Social Network Coordinator Note: Contact lists for volunteers might be shared with delegates & volunteers within OIFE on a need to know basis.Subscribers to OIFE MagazineWhat kind of data we storeIf you are a professional or not (Yes / No)NameE-mailPurpose of the data: Distribution of OIFE Magazine via e-mail. Who can access the data: OIFE’s administration. Note: When an individual contacts the OIFE by e-mail, we ask for consent from the person to be included in our list of subscribers of the OIFE Magazine.Professionals who work with OIWhat kind of data we storeNameE-mailWorkplaceWork address (address, city, zip code, country)DepartmentSpecialtyPhoneSource of the data:Subscription to OIFE MagazinePersonal contact via e-mail with OIFE officeParticipation in conferences hosted by OIFE or one of our partnersThe purposes of the databaseAdministration of OIFE’s Medical Advisory BoardDistribution of OIFE MagazineDistribution of invitation to conferences & information about grantsTool for OIFE’s Social Network Coordinator in assisting individuals in finding local support & doctors with experience in OIAccess to data: OIFE Administration & OIFE Social Network Coordinator Note: When a professional contacts the OIFE by e-mail, we ask for consent from the person to be included in our list of subscribers of the OIFE Magazine.DonorsWhat kind of data we storeNameContact informationPayment information once the transaction is complete (needed for our financial reports).Purpose of the database:Financial reportsDistribution of OIFE MagazineAccess to data: OIFE Administration Note: When a person donates money to the OIFE, we ask for consent from the person to be included in our list of subscribers of the OIFE Magazine.Corporate PartnersNameE-mailWorkplacePhoneSource of the data:Subscription to OIFE MagazinePersonal contact via e-mail with OIFE officeParticipation in conferences hosted by OIFE or one of our partnersThe purposes of the databaseDistribution of OIFE MagazineContact regarding research and developmentFundraisings purposesTool for the Medical Advisory BoardAccess to data: OIFE president, OIFE secretary and OIFE Treasurer Note: When a corporate representative contacts the OIFE by e-mail, we ask for consent from the person to be included in our list of subscribers of the OIFE Magazine.Right to be deletedUnless we need your data for our financial reports (which we are obliged to store a number of years), you have the right to ask to have your name and contact information deleted from all our lists. Individuals may ask for their information to be deleted from our contact lists by contacting the OIFE at office@oife.org.Unless you specifically ask us to do so, we will NOT delete you from historical participant lists or other files which are no longer in use for distribution of news/information.OIFE eventWhen OIFE host events, we produce participant lists with information we need to host the event. Access is depending on who’s in charge of the event. After the event, the participant lists are moved from the various project folders to the folder containing personal data.When hosting events, we ask for permission in the registration forms regarding photos and videos – for later use in OIFE Magazine, webpage, social media or written publications.Visitors to our webpageUnless you have do-not-track enabled in your browser, we collect anonymous, non-identifiable information about visitors such as operating system and web browser type/version as well as the time and date of your visit on a particular page. The information automatically recorded by our server is used only for statistical purposes so that we can manage our site better and serve our visitors. All information provided by users is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. Our site uses cookies to uniquely identify users’ machines so that we can monitor site usage, traffic and trends.Opt-out complete; your visits to this website will not be recorded by the Web Analytics tool. Note that if you clear your cookies, delete the opt-out cookie, or if you change computers or Web browsers, you will need to perform the opt-out procedure again.You may choose to prevent this website from aggregating and analyzing the actions you take here. Doing so will protect your privacy, but will also prevent the owner from learning from your actions and creating a better experience for you and other users.
You are not opted out. Uncheck this box to opt-out. You are currently opted out. Check this box to opt-in. The tracking opt-out feature requires cookies to be enabled.More information about privacy?Should a user require additional information regarding the OI Foundation’s privacy policies or practices, or how information is collected and used on the site, please contact OIFE by e-mail at office@oife.org or the address listed below:Osteogenesis Imperfecta Federation Europe Schotelveldstraat 17,
2801 Heffen,
Belgium  OIFE - Osteogenesis Imperfecta Federation EuropeOIFE PassportPrivacyDisclaimer Translate »
